{
  "id": 401,
  "themeId": 4,
  "name": "Writing and Reading Gender Test 1",
  "description": "Autogenerated quiz",
  "version": "2.2.1",
  "lastUpdated": "13/04/2025",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "How do you say “She”?",
      "options": [
        "Elle",
        "Sa",
        "Lui",
        "All of the above"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Elle",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say “He”?",
      "options": [
        "Lui",
        "Il",
        "Ils",
        "Leur"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Il",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say “They”? (plural, feminine)",
      "options": [
        "Elle",
        "Elles",
        "Ellent",
        "Eles"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Elles",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say “His”?",
      "options": [
        "Son",
        "Sa",
        "Le",
        "Lui"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Son",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say \"The\"? (singular, feminine)",
      "options": [
        "Sa",
        "Leur",
        "La",
        "Les"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "La",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say \"The\"? (singular, masculine)",
      "options": [
        "Lui",
        "Les",
        "Son",
        "Le"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Le",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say \"Her motorcycle\"?",
      "options": [
        "Sa moto",
        "La moto",
        "Son moto",
        "Elle moto"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Sa moto",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say \"His death\"?",
      "options": [
        "Son mort",
        "Sa mort",
        "Leur mort",
        "Il est mort"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Sa mort",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say \"her hair\" ?",
      "options": [
        "Son cheveux",
        "Sa cheveu",
        "Ses cheveux",
        "Leur cheveu"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Ses cheveux",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say “They”?  (plural, non binary)",
      "options": [
        "Iels",
        "Yels",
        "Elils",
        "All of the above"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "All of the above",
      "explanation": ""
    }
  ]
}